♪ In the not-too-distant future
♪ Somewhere in time and space
♪ Mike Nelson and his robot pals
♪ Are caught in an endless chase
♪ Pursued by a woman
whose name is Pearl
♪ An evil gal who
wants to rule the world
♪ She threw a few
things in her purse
♪ And in her rocketship
she hunts them
♪ All across the universe
- [Pearl] I'll get you!
♪ I'll send them cheesy movies
♪ The worst I can find
♪ La-La-La
♪ They'll have to sit
and watch them all
♪ And the monitor is mine
♪ La-La-La
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control
♪ Where the movies begin or end
♪ La-La-La
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity
♪ With the help of
his robot friends
♪ Robot roll call
♪ Cambot
- You're on!
♪ Gypsy
- Oh my stars!
♪ Tom Servo
- Check me out.
♪ Croooow
- I'm different.
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♪ And other science facts
♪ La-La-La
♪ Just repeat to
yourself, it's just a show
♪ I should really just relax
♪ For Mystery
Science Theater 3000
(doors slamming)
- Well, I'm sorry, Mike.
- Well, there, you
just did it again.
- What the?
- Hi, everyone, welcome
to the Satellite of Love.
Servo and I here,
we're just talking.
- Look, I didn't mean to turn
you on, and I'm really sorry!
- Well, you know ever
since Robert Palmer
introduced the concept of
accidental turn-ons in his song
I Didn't Mean To Turn You On,
well, there's been a lot of
involuntary on-turning
around here.
- Hey there guys, what's up?
- Crow!
- Oh, no, did I just
turn you on again?
- Yes, you know you did, geez!
- I am sorry.
I tried not to turn you on,
but I guess I
unintentionally did.
- You know, let's all try
to be a little more careful
about turning each
other on, okay?
- That's sure, Mike.
- Right, Mike.
- And you folks at home
be a little more careful.
Don't involuntarily
turn anyone on, okay?
We'll be right back.
- [Both] Mike!
- Did I turn you on?
I didn't mean to, look at me!
How do I turn you on?
I'm just standing here,
how did I turn you on?
Why are you?
- Now, there!
There, you did so mean
to turn me on that time!
- Okay, I admit it, I turned
you on on purpose, okay?
Because I was upset, so I
turned you on, so big deal!
- Well, now you
just turned me on!
Can't you do anything
without turning people on?
- Oh, that's nice,
coming from you,
after you turned me on.
- I did not!
- Yes, you did!
- You turned around
and turned me on!
- You couldn't turn me on if
you had a dozen naked Gerardos
and Fabio in tight
leather pants.
(gasping)
Where was I?
Oh, right.
I'm remodeling the Great Hall.
I'm putting in a
conversation pit,
and the couch I had picked
out for it came in early,
so I need you guys
to store it for me.
Brain Guy?
- Yes, madam?
(pop)
- And no jumping on the couch.
- [All] Whee!
- Jumping!
- Thanks, Grandma Pearl!
- Watch, you guys, I'm
gonna do something cool.
You can see my legs!
- Gramma Pearl does not want
you jumping on that couch!
Get off, right now!
Don't squeeze those juice
boxes on that couch!
(gleeful laughter)
- We're squirting it all
over everything, it's great!
- Oh, we can't have nice things!
That's it, that is it.
I am going to give
you such a movie.
- [All] We don't care!
- Bobo?
Brain Guy?
Get the movie.
- (gasping) No!
(terror-filled scream)
(confused laughing)
- We have ways of dealing
with ne'er-do-wells
who insist on jumping on
our rent-to-own couches.
Your movie
(terror-filled scream)
is called
(box creaking)
Hobgoblins!
(terror-filled scream)
- Pearl, please.
Whatever you're
thinking, please don't--
- We've been--
- It was Mike's fault,
he made us do it!
I'm sorry!
(alarm buzzing)
- Movie sign!
(sobbing softly)
- [Mike] I'm scared.
- [Servo] Hey, presents!
Good!
- [Mike] Well, that should be.
- [Servo] Oh, no.
- [Mike] I'm very afraid.
- [Crow] Ah,
badly-lit warehouse.
I feel better already.
(crunchy footsteps)
- [Mike] He got
Pringles in his shoes?
- [Servo] Proof that
janitors walk upright.
- [Crow] The true
story of Neal Peart.
(imitating music)
- Dennis?
Dennis!
- [Mike] I wanna play tennis!
- Hey!
What gives?
- You're being paid
to work around here,
not to sit around and
blast your eardrums!
- Hey, hey, take it easy.
I can do both.
(telephone ringing)
- [Servo] This is
Coach's brother here?
- Hello?
Hello?
- [Crow] Uhhhhhhhhh.
- Didn't you hear
the phone ringing?
- Oh, no, I didn't.
- They've already hung up!
- Well, then it couldn't
have been too important, huh?
- Don't you have any
sense of responsibility?
That could have been
a very important call!
- At this hour?
- In the future, would
you just answer the phone
no matter what hour it is,
and not make your
own decisions about
what's important and what isn't?
- Yeah, yeah, right, right.
It's time for our rounds.
- [Mike] Oh, they're doctors.
Oh, okay, I got it.
- [Crow] Yeah, uh huh.
- [Servo] D'oh.
- [Crow] Dammit,
why aren't you old?
- [Servo] He's the abusive
grampa I never had.
- [Mike] Cameraman just
can't get up the energy
to get over there.
- [Crow] In here's my
secret stash of Cheetos,
Dr. Pepper, and back
issues of Cosmo.
- [Servo] Jimmy Stewart and
Rex Smith in Breaking In.
- [Mike] He's really my mentor.
He taught me how to
truly love a woman
from across the street,
through a telescope.
- [Crow] Yup, I used to
be Robert Frost, y'know?
- [Servo] So, it's a
security guard training film.
- [Mike] You know, I
think we actually are
fully-qualified
security guards now.
- [Crow] I'd love to
get out of the rat race
and guard a U-Store-It
for a while.
That'd be great.
- [Servo] I just want
to measure and see
if you'll fit in
the incinerator.
- [Crow] It's weird to
think we were once married.
- Did I ever tell you
what this studio was like
when I first started here?
- Yeah, more than once.
- Oh, it used to be one of
the busiest lots in town.
- It's a real thriving
metropolis now.
- [Mike] Oh man, his
pants are coming at me!
Oh!
- [Servo] Whoa!
- Wait a minute,
what's this down here?
- Oh, it's, it's just
an old filled-in wall.
There's nothing down there.
- Well, yeah, why don't
we check it anyway?
- [Mike] No!
- I'm telling you, there's
nothing down there,
and I'm not going to waste
my time checking it out!
- [Mike] Pants, away!
- [Radio] McCreedy?
- What is it now?
- [Radio] I need to
talk to you, now!
- Well, I can't right now!
- [Radio] Now!
I mean it.
- [Servo] I'm
colicky, get in here!
- And remember what I said.
- Hey, whatever you say, Pops.
- [Mike] Okay, then I say
dress in hot pants from now on.
- [Crow] Whoa,
what is that stain?
- [Servo] Ooh.
- [Mike] Is he thawing a box
of frozen peas under his arm?
- [Servo] Okay, so what, now
he becomes a Jedi knight?
Why am I sitting here?
- [Mike] Take it
easy, take it easy.
- [Crow] Man, that
stain was unbelievable.
(terror-filled music)
- [Servo] He's playing
the organ with his head.
(imitating organ sounds)
- [Mike] That bank
door killed a man.
(gate squeaking)
- So there's nothing down here?
- [Servo] You wily old fox.
(terror-filled musical cue)
Wonder what they keep in here.
- [Mike] It's a secret
blow-comb storehouse.
- Yoo-hoo!
Mr. McCreedy?
- [Servo] I need
another Yoo-hoo!
Whoa.
- [Crow] Wow.
I wonder if he knows his
face looks like that.
- [Mike] He can't.
- [Crow] Should tell him.
- [Mike] Oh, Burgess
Meredith's in there reading.
- [Servo] (groaning) My sunken
chest and string-beany arms!
- [Crow] Maybe The Great Carnac
answers are stored in there.
- [All] Yes!
- [Mike] Okay, yeah, yup,
go all the way in there.
Slam the door firmly
behind you, and die, good.
(gate door creaks)
- [Crow] Ah, these
honor system banks
are just never gonna make it.
- [Mike] This poor
guy was edged out of
every decent role
by Grant Goodeve.
- [Servo] Is he gonna
get mauled by $100 bills?
Do something!
(guttural growling)
- [Mike] Huh?
Wow, shouldn't
have skipped lunch.
- Is somebody here?
(guttural growling)
- [Crow] I mean,
besides you, Cerebus.
(guttural growling)
- [Mike] Oh, David
Crosby's eating in there.
- Is somebody there?
- [Servo] Does he have
his pants on backwards?
- [Crow] Leif
Garrett in The Rose.
(shrill feedback)
- [Mike] Ladies and
gentlemen, Flatbutt.
(audience cheering)
- [Servo] You know, he's
already got Loverboy
beat as a live act.
(pop rock music playing)
- [Crow] Yep, now his big rock
anthem about minimum wage.
(everyone groaning)
- [Mike] You know,
this is a real cheap
biopic of Jim Morrison.
♪ We're on the road to nowhere
- [Servo] I'll say.
♪ Come on inside
- [Mike] Oh, the show's
starting, yay, yay, yay!
- [Servo] Mike, if
I run out of vomit,
can I have some of yours?
- [Crow] Ugh.
Oh, just sing the St.
Elmo's Fire theme song,
and get it over with!
(screaming)
- [Mike] Oh, he
tried to crowd surf,
but no one wanted to touch him.
- [Servo] Hey, it's Carl Lewis!
Oh, no.
- [Crow] Yeah, it's the old guy.
(scary music)
The crowd threw
beef gravy on him.
- [Mike] Oh, poor kid, and
he had so little promise.
- [Servo] Member, FDI-Murder!
- [Crow] Death guaranteed
for up to 50,000 die!
- [Mike] Oh, good one.
Oh, what do I put on
my time sheet for this?
- [Servo] Hey, the end credits!
Well, it was a terrible movie.
At least it was short.
- [Mike] These are
the beginning credits.
- [Servo] Oh, well,
then kill me, please?
Please?
- [Crow] Ah, the king
of the Wisconsin Dells
finally gets a movie.
- [Servo] Paige Sullivan!
- [Crow] Steven Boggs
this whole movie down.
- [Mike] That's good.
Ah, the cheap sequel
to Billy Jack.
(meek laughter)
Frank.
- [Crow] Is she related
to Wacky T-Bakke?
(feeble laughter)
I'm leaving, I just--
- [Mike] No, Crow,
come on now, come back.
Just don't try so hard.
Come on, here.
- [Crow] Kari French!
(laughing) I bet she
loves that dressing!
Sorry, I hate myself, goodbye!
- [Mike] Crow, get back here!
- [Servo] James Mayberry, RFD!
Oh, I hate myself, too!
- [Mike] Come on,
get back in here.
Come on, hey, Servo, no!
Come back.
- [Crow] I can't!
I can't, Mike, I'm outta here.
- [Mike] Sit back, sit!
Oh, Crow!
- [Crow] (sobbing)
No, I can't take it!
- [Mike] Come back and sit down.
Sit, come, get!
Get, no, get back in here!
Sit down!
Come on.
(Servo sobbing)
No, don't!
Come back here.
(Crow sobbing)
No, no, we're gonna sit down.
We're gonna calm down.
We're gonna watch this movie.
- [Servo] D'oh!
- [Crow] D'oh!
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme song)
- So, Kevin, is
this the first time
that you've worked
as a security guard?
- Yes, sir.
But I'm a very fast learner,
and I promise to try extra hard,
and I really need the job.
- [Mike] And I have
a Ph. D in security.
- You sound very
mature for your age.
- [Servo] Aw, schucks!
- You don't own one of
those portable radios
with the headphones, do you?
- [Crow] Or one of those
horseless carriages.
- That's good.
I think we'll get
along just fine.
- [Servo] Huh, ha, schucks!
- Are you ready for your
first tour of the lot?
- Oh, yes, sir.
Even prepared to take notes.
- It's not that complicated.
- [Mike] JFK Jr. could do it.
- [Servo] These are the stairs.
Stairs are your
hips' worst enemies.
- You've never been
on a studio lot
like this before, have you?
- No, sir.
- Well, it's not that
difficult to keep track of.
There isn't much goes on here.
- [Mike] Pants again.
- How long have you
been working here?
- Oh, quite a while.
- [Servo] Pants in your face!
- About 30 years, actually,
and I've never missed a day
and had to have
someone fill in for me.
- [Crow] Pathetic.
- 30 years?
That's amazing!
- Well, not really.
You know, time
becomes sort of a blur
when you reach a certain age.
- [Servo] Uh huh.
- Sometime, I'll tell you
what this place was like
when it was still a
functioning studio.
- I'd like to hear about that.
- [Crow] I'll also
tell you about
my problematic urethra,
if you'll follow me.
- [Servo] Yes, we
paid for this wing
with the profits from D.C. Cab.
- Now, Kevin, if I told you that
something was very
important to this studio,
would you--
- Of course.
- Now, there is a
part of this lot
I want you to stay away from.
I don't want to have to
explain all the details to you.
I just want you to promise
to stay clear from it.
- I understand.
- [Mike] And I don't
really care, anyway.
- Now this is the part
I was telling you about.
- [Servo] This is where we keep
Clint Howard and
Michael J. Pollard.
- What's down there?
- Oh, it's just a lot
of dangerous machinery.
Now, don't go in there
and take the chance
of injuring yourself.
Do you understand?
- Yeah.
- Good.
Now, I don't want to have
to remind you a second time!
Just stay clear from this area.
- [Crow] In fact,
just sit at your desk
and don't do anything.
- [Mike] Sometimes
Catherine Hepburn shows up.
We have to chase her outta here.
- So is there anything else
I need to be made aware of?
- There is one other thing.
- [Servo] You should
know you'll have to apply
a series of ointments
to me regularly.
- [Crow] He's got his
outdoor eyebrows on now.
(Mike laughing)
- This is what I was
telling you about.
- [Mike] Use it to kill
Archduke Ferdinand.
- Oh, but don't worry.
I've never had to use it.
- Really?
- That's right, but in all
the years I've been here.
- [Servo] Had to wing
Gloria Swanson once.
- I would like to show you
how to use it sometime.
Look, you never know
when you might need it.
- [Crow] You never
know when a relay race
will show up at the front gate.
- [Mike] Smells like Jack Ruby.
- [Servo] (sighs) I resign.
The best words I ever said.
- [Crow] Paint my muscle
car prune-colored, please.
- [Mike] Wow, the
Dangerous Loner Model Home.
- Hi.
- Not now.
Your friends are here.
- [Servo] How do
you read a record?
- Hey, how's it going?
- [Crow] Well, come over there
so you can maybe answer me.
- What'd you bring,
some new music?
- No, I just rented a video tape
that Amy and I were gonna watch.
- Well, that was very nice.
Let me see what you got.
What?
Don't you ever get any tapes
from the adult section?
My boyfriend would
never bring me a tape
that didn't have at
least a single X rating.
- Well, Kevin isn't like that.
He would never want me to see
anything that was rated X.
Would you?
- No, I wouldn't.
- [Mike] Scram, it's
the owner of the house!
We have to shoot the
movie somewhere else!
(horn honking)
- [Servo] Fresh-a fish!
- Oh, right, man,
I'd recognize that horn
anywhere, that's my Nick,
back from two months
of Army training,
and you know what a man wants
when he's been away
for two months.
- No, what does he want?
- Whooooooo!
- [Mike] Belly dancing lessons?
(imitating squeaking)
- [Mike] Oh, dear.
Ugh.
- [Servo] Ohh!
- Two months!
- [Mike] So, that was sex?
- Whoa, everybody
have sex tonight.
- [Servo] Everybody
throw up tonight.
- Wish I were up
to do something.
- Did you say something?
- No, no.
- [Crow] Ironically, no
one in the band Wang Chung
had sex that night.
- [Mike] Did Mark
Rothko do this room?
- Oh yeah, then we
spend all afternoon
studying hand-to-hand combat!
- I know about the techniques
you have with your hands.
Tell us about something else.
(Crow retching)
- Yeah, could we change
the subject already?
- Why don't you pay attention,
and maybe you'll
learn something?
Nick is protecting our country,
and you're just guarding
some run-down deserted dump.
- What did you say?
- Why don't you be nice to Nick,
and maybe he'll
teach you something?
- Maybe I could teach you all
about hand-to-hand combat?
No problem!
- Yeah!
- Go on, I know you can do it.
- Look, I said I wasn't
interested, okay?
- Come on!
- [Servo] I want to get away
from Skull Woman, anyway!
- [Mike] You know,
this place has
real garbage house potential.
- I don't want to do this.
- Here, take this.
- [Crow] Choose
your garden weasel!
- No, no, no, hold it like this!
- [Servo] Full-contact
mulching, I guess.
- Okay, now block
every move that I make.
I'm gonna take it
really slow on you.
Watch out, 'cause here
comes the first one!
- [Servo] Wow.
- Go, Nick, kick his butt!
- [Mike] Yeah, give him a
big, rusty gash in his head!
Come on!
- [Crow] Can we have a
law that, in the future,
films have to be
made by filmmakers?
- [Servo] Is that a condom she
has hanging from her blouse?
- I'm getting so sweaty already.
- [Mike] So we sent our
armies to the Gulf War
with garden shovels
and grass rollers?
- [Crow] Their garden tools
make little Casio sounds.
- Yeah, go for it!
- [Servo] Yeah, really,
really kill him!
Please.
(grunts)
- [Mike] You know, I'd switch
to the weed whacker
at this point.
- [Crow] Throw some
Miracle-Gro in his eyes!
- [Servo] I'm gonna
compost you, man.
- [Mike] (sigh) Oh, the tension.
Will they water their lawn?
- [Servo] Wow.
- [Crow] Ever.
I'll bet Nick can also field
strip his rake blindfolded.
- [Servo] This movie's
making me nostalgic
for the film Gymkata.
- [Mike] Nope, it just happened.
Did you see that, the
hose out-acted him.
- [Crow] Did you know
that Nick went on to play
Pong in his underwear
while drinking beer?
- [Servo] Hey, hooray, you
ruptured his spleen, yay!
- [Mike] Now I'm gonna
remove your thatch.
- [Servo] Don't let them
hurt my red shorts, please.
Wow.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Mike] I could
watch this forever,
and I have a feeling
I probably will be.
- [Robots] Yep.
- [Crow] So does Hardware Hank
have a major defense
contract, or?
- [Mike] He's also a black
belt in whack-a-mole.
- [Servo] Ha ha, that's neat!
Welcome home, Nick!
- You give up?
- Yes!
- [Crow] Now Nick's gonna
declare martial law,
loot his museums, and
call in an airstrike.
- My hero!
(Mike and the robots groaning)
- [Servo] Wow.
- [Mike] Ugh, there hasn't
been such a glorious battle
since the Arnold Stang/Wally
Cox fight of 1958.
- You really humiliated me.
- What?
I didn't even want to do this.
- [Servo] Oh, look, ugh!
(Servo retching)
- I don't care whose idea
it was, I wanted you to win.
- How was I supposed
to win, Amy?
I've never even
done this before.
It was an unfair match.
- You looked really pathetic.
- [Crow] Okay, grab
a rake, let's go!
- What do you want
me to do for you?
- I want you to make me proud.
- [Mike] Pee-Wee
Herman casual wear.
- [Servo] Made love
in a Chevy van,
and that's not alright with me!
- [Crow] Or me.
(joyful laughter)
(doors slamming)
- Say, Mike.
Given the incredibly
depraved attitude
regarding women
in today's movie,
I'd knew you want me
to make a short film
for boys and young
men teaching them
how to treat the fair sex with
a proper and healthy respect.
Mike?
Mike!
- Yeah, sure.
- So, good, 'cause I went
ahead and did it anyway,
and hopefully it'll
help just a little.
Let's watch.
Ah, women.
Women, women, women,
women, women, women, women.
For you young fellows
fresh on the cusp
of a blooming manhood,
the questions abound.
What are women like?
What do women want?
How should I treat a woman?
Perhaps the thorniest
problem facing any young man
is finding a woman
in the first place.
It turned out to be
nearly impossible.
This reporter spent countless
hours searching for a woman,
like these pictured
here, to no avail.
The nearest we came during a
tense stakeout was this fellow,
who experts believe
is not a woman.
We begin to wonder,
where are all the women?
The overheated
references in poetry.
The images that
dominate our media.
Is it all an elaborate fraud?
This grainy photograph is the
only direct evidence we have
of a woman in her
natural environment.
The longer hair, the gentle
and nurturing demeanor
are typical of how
witnesses describe
their supposed
encounters with women.
This footprint, while possibly
the work of jokesters,
is another piece of the puzzle,
and it is hard to discount
this man's terrifying story.
- And then, uh, this woman.
Well, I think it was a woman,
she, uh, married me.
- [Crow voiceover] Did you
have any children, sir?
- I don't remember.
- Some day perhaps, an
actual woman will emerge,
and they will no longer exist
only in the realm
of myth and maybe.
Thank you.
Ahhh.
Oh, um, yes, so, anyway,
Mike, in conclusion,
in the off-chance that
you do run into a woman,
you know, treat her
with respect and stuff.
- You know, Crow,
you do know women.
What about Pearl?
- Okay, so one woman exists.
That means all women exist?
- We'll be right back.
- Name me one other woman.
- Well, act--
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- What's the matter, Kevin?
- [Servo] I got a
three on the G.E.D.
- It's really a long story.
- I've got all the
time in the world.
- [Crow] Oh, okay, then.
"Call me Ishmael.
"I--"
- What do you do about someone
who you can never make happy?
- [Mike] Son, you
make me very happy.
- Is this your girlfriend
we're talking about?
- [Crow] No, I can't
make my hamster happy.
What do you think?!
- I don't know what to tell you.
What's the exact problem?
- [Servo] Can I
loosen her up for you?
- Well, we've got this
friend who's in the Army.
- [Crow] Omar Bradley?
- And my girlfriend's upset,
because I couldn't do all
the things that he can.
- [Mike] Like join
racist groups.
- I see.
Did I ever tell you what I
did when I was in the Army?
- [Servo] I was Tokyo Rose.
- No.
- Well, it's also a long story.
(long beep)
- [Crow] Oh, that'll
be Kevorkian.
- Uh oh.
Looks like we've got company.
- [Mike] Ah, and some
guy sneaking around
like a silent film villain.
- [Servo] Looks like Dana Gould.
- Hey.
- Wait here.
I'll call you if I need you.
- But Mr. McCreedy!
- I said to wait!
- [Crow] Turn on
your baby minder.
- [Mike] Hey, the
Kirk Cameron Show!
- [Servo] Well, it's the same
speed on the Ventura Freeway.
- [Crow] Bullitt,
now for seniors.
- [Mike] I'll get
that guy, but first,
I'll just stop at the
Bishop's Buffet here.
♪ Take on me
♪ Take me on
- [Crow] Oh, I forgot
what I was doing.
- Oh!
- Shut up.
- [Mike] Oh, I don't like
the "old guy getting
killed" channel.
- [Servo] If found, please
return to Hunter Thompson.
- [Crow] I don't like the way
you greeted me at Wal-Mart.
- Get away from him.
- [Mike] You Menendez
brother wannabe!
- Is this your grandson?
- No, he's my part--
- I said--
- [Crow] Darn, what
was it again I said?
- Get away from him.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- Who you kidding?
You don't know how to use that.
- [Servo] Alright, so I
didn't plug it in, you got me.
Marks?
- [Crow] Oh, great,
you just took out
Air Force One, you dope.
(McCreedy coughing)
- Are you okay?
You want me to
call an ambulance?
- No, no, I'm fine.
- Damn!
- What's the matter?
- I just wish Amy
could have been here
to see what I just did.
- [Mike] I shot a starter pistol
and whined out another line!
- He's still on the lot.
- What do we do now?
- I'm going to call the police.
Try to locate where he is,
but keep a distance from him.
Don't try to be a hero.
(Servo whines feebly)
- [Servo] I'd
better call Grandma.
Tell her I'm okay.
- [Mike] This is
Captain Kangaroo.
Come in, Mr. Moose.
- [Crow] So did the
ad for the job read,
"Wanted, whiny half-wit coward?"
- [Mike] I just want to be brave
for my horrible, frigid,
non-supportive girlfriend!
(Servo whining feebly)
- [Servo] When I find him,
I'm gonna make him
sign in so bad.
- [Crow] Serpico.
Dirty Harry.
Jake Gittes.
Kevin.
- [Mike] This place is
packed with garden tools!
- Mr. McCreedy?
- [Crow] Hello?
Hello, hello?
- [Kevin] Where all
the machinery is?
- [Crow] No.
- I think he went down there.
I'm going in for a closer look.
- [Servo] Hello, who's this?
- [Mike] Sit, stay.
- [Crow] Carl Sandburg, P.I.
- What?
What?
- [Servo] I've got lobby against
Medicare cuts immediately!
- Kevin!
Stop whatever you're doing!
Don't go near the vault,
no matter what you do.
Don't go near the vault.
- [Mike] This is
Old Guy Radio, WOLD.
♪ W, o, l, d
- [Servo] The vault
turned 21 in prison,
doing life without parole.
- [Crow] Sister Kevin Prejean.
- Amy.
I wanna make you proud.
- [Servo] I'm gonna break
into Jack Benny's piggy bank.
- [Mike] Tell me again why
they have an elaborate
security system
if they don't lock anything?
- [Servo] I don't know.
- [Crow] Ah, he's found
Ben Stein's money.
- [Mike] This is where the
years of mall walking pays off!
- [Crow] I mean,
they don't even have
a twist tie on the door.
- [Servo] Script to
Billy Madison 2 is
kept hidden in here.
- [Mike] Ow, what
am I doing, ow, ow!
Oh, I crushed
myself, I'm crushed.
I'm dead.
- [Servo] Where did I leave
my egg salad sandwich?
- [Mike] Hmm, locked?
Nah.
- [Crow] Buddy
Ebsen, triathlete.
- [Servo] Papillon?
Hi, the door was open.
(guttural growling)
- [Mike] Oh, Taz got out.
- Oh, we're too late!
Kevin, why did you come in here?
Why didn't you listen to me?
- [Crow] 'Cause
you're really old.
I mean, would you listen to you?
- [Servo] Enough with
the Count Chocula music!
Geez.
- [Mike] Take it
easy, take it easy.
Come on, follow me
to the band room!
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
(running footsteps)
- What's going on?
- [Mike] Ah, hobgoblins,
four hours in.
- [Crow] Look what they've
done with Casey Martin!
- [Servo] Oh, thunder road!
(guttural growling)
- [Mike] Yeah, real smooth
ride, good steering, I like it.
- [Crow] I went to Michael
Spinks' barber, okay?
- [Servo] Here, try
some pole dancing!
- [Mike] They ripped
out the tape player!
- Oh, if you only knew
what you just did.
- I don't understand!
What just happened?
- The vault.
I tried to warn you.
Those creatures.
The vault!
I tried!
- [Crow] Sentence fragments!
Just phrases!
- All my work!
30 years, I've been trying to
prevent this from happening.
- To prevent what
from happening?
- Those creatures.
Why do you think I spent the
last 30 years of my life here?
- [Crow] Low SATs?
- I was keeping
them from escaping.
- [Servo] A-a-a-aping.
- I was young when I
began to work here.
The studio was busy
and prosperous.
- [Mike] Now I sound
like Joseph Campbell.
- [McCreedy voiceover]
I'll always remember
the night that it happened.
- [Crow] Golf carts
were bigger then.
- [McCreedy voiceover] There
was hardly anyone around.
- [Tom] William Holden
had just passed out.
- [McCreedy voiceover]
I didn't even know
what it was at first.
It was oh so fast,
just a flash of light
and a sudden explosion.
I stepped out to
see what it was.
There was no one else
there except for me.
- [Mike] I had the popular Jerry
Orbach hairstyle back then.
- [McCreedy voiceover]
It was right
in the middle of the lot.
If it'd been daytime,
it probably would have been
crushed in all the traffic.
I just stared at
it for a long time.
I didn't know what
to make of it.
And then suddenly, it moved.
Out of the top of the disc
came this small creature,
sort of hobgoblin.
It looked around,
and then it stared right at me.
- [Crow] At this point,
I hadn't yet reacted.
- [McCreedy voiceover]
I didn't move.
I just kept watching it.
- [Servo] Yep, yep, that's
true, that's what happened.
Yep, yep, uh huh, uh
huh, yep yep yep, uh huh.
- [McCreedy voiceover] If
only I'd known what lay ahead.
- [Mike] But that's Monday
morning security guarding.
- But I still don't understand.
- I let the creatures
live on the lot.
It was my secret.
And then I learned of
the power they had.
I still don't know if
they figured they were
doing good for people or not.
- [Crow] So I married
one to check it out.
- They slowly began to
destroy everyone on the lot.
They would find a person,
tap into his brain,
and then create his
wildest fantasy.
It seemed harmless at first.
I mean, watching everyone
around you becoming
rich or famous, but,
but most people, what
they really wanted,
life can be very dangerous.
In fact, the creatures wound
up destroying everyone.
Everyone they came
in contact with.
- [Mike] Luckily, all I
wanted was a good Thermos.
- They're loose in the city now.
- But you could warn everyone.
They'd listen to your story.
- Would they?
You know, maybe 30 years ago,
I went straight to
the head of the studio
and tried to explain it to him.
He didn't believe me.
No one did.
(Servo yawning)
I just watched helplessly
as people around
me were destroyed
one by one.
- [Crow] But (feeble whining)
- What can we do?
- Why, I'm too old to
catch up with them now,
but you might still
have a chance.
There aren't very many of
them, but they move quickly.
Just remember,
they're attracted
to bright lights.
That's how you can find them.
(Crow whines feebly)
Watch everyone around you.
If a person begins
to act strangely,
it means that one
of the creatures
have tapped into his mind.
When this happens, the
creature is never far away.
Find it and kill it
before it's too late,
because when the creature dies,
the fantasy ends and
the victim is safe.
- [Crow] Well.
- Now remember, they're only
attracted to bright light.
That's how you find them,
but you must destroy
them all before dawn,
because once it's
daylight, it's too late.
- [Mike] Right, bright light.
- You'll never be
able to stop them.
- [Crow] Great, Gramps.
I'm gonna go see if
the Colonel's hiring.
(sinister music)
- [Mike] Huh, he never asked
me about my grandchildren.
(record scratching)
- [Crow] Hey, don't
scratch the quarterflash!
- [Servo] Why the
Ross Perot doll?
(energetic pop music)
♪ It's the '80s
♪ Do a lot of coke and
vote for Ronald Reagan
- [Servo] Ugh, Larry Wilcox is
gonna make a cameo, isn't he?
- [Crow] Say, is that
Haircut 100 they're playing?
(guttural growling)
♪ Invest in arbitrage
and read Jay McInerney
- Come on, Amy, would
you get with it?
- [Crow] I think we stumbled
on to Mel's Rock Pile.
(excited growling)
- [Servo] Meet the
hobgoblins, Frankie, Sniffles,
Bounce-Bounce, and The Claw!
- [Mike] On two, and break!
- [Crow] Oh, they're
having an all-girls night.
(car horn honking)
- Ah, the car horn!
I recognize it anywhere!
Ahh!
- [Servo] Ooh.
- [Mike] Ugh.
- [Servo] Make that three
hard-boiled eggs, heh heh!
(car horn honking)
- See you guys later.
- [Mike] Okay, Olive Oyl.
- Much later.
- [Servo] Ooh.
- That's weird.
- [Crow] I'm not
having sex right now.
- Maybe he's circling
the block or something.
- [Servo] She looks
like Michael Bolton.
- I brought your jacket.
I thought you might
be cold out here.
- Yeah, thanks a lot.
- [Mike] Thanks for
your stinking kindness.
- Where's Nick?
I thought I heard
his horn before.
(Crow babbling like Jerry Lewis)
- Maybe you should wait
inside until you see him.
- He's just looking
- [Servo] Whoopee, whoo-hoo!
- for a place to park.
Go back in the house.
- There's plenty of
parking in front.
Maybe it wasn't his horn.
- Look, I'm positive it was.
Maybe the police pulled him
over for his horn or something.
You know, just go
back in the house.
- Fine, I get the message.
- Just take this
stupid jacket with you.
- [Mike] You and your stupid
thoughtfulness can go to hell!
(Crow making goofy sounds)
- Damn it, Nick, where
the hell are you?
- [Crow] It's a praying
mantis in a party dress!
Oh no, it's her, sorry.
- [Mike] Anybody out
here will do, really.
- [Crow] Ah, Don King!
(guttural growling)
- Amy, would you just
go back in the house,
and leave me alone?
- [Servo] I see your
point, yes, I agree.
- Would you stop
breathing all over me?
(fierce growl)
(screaming)
- [Mike] Can't you see what
I'm trying to tell you?
I love you.
- Sounds like Nick
finally got here.
- [Servo] Oh!
- [Crow] Oh no, we're
simply depending
on the integrity of the
fabric at this point.
- [Mike] Look, I'm
trying to get off you.
My claws are stuck,
could you help out?
- She must be happy to see him.
- [Servo] Please make there be
titanium control panels
on those pantyhose.
- [Crow] The historic first
meeting of Luke and Laura.
- Take that!
- [Mike] Work him into the
soil, that's right, yup.
- [Servo] When threatened,
she gains the strength
of a thousand trollops.
(strained grunting)
- [Crow] Tell 'em
Laraine Newman's in town.
- [Mike] After my date with
Prince, I went right home.
(Daphne groaning)
- Honestly, couldn't Nick wait?
- [Servo] Who's this Nick?
Is there another
man in your life?
- What's going on?
(screaming)
- [Crow] Someone's
rubbing puppets on us!
- [Servo] Man.
- [Mike] You know,
Nick's a fun guy,
but he parallel parks so slowly.
- [Servo] Koala
bears are attacking!
- [Crow] We hate Qantas, grrr!
(panicked screaming)
- [Mike] There's a
girl touching me, yuck!
- [Servo] If you'd just let
go, they'll hit the floor!
- [Crow] One of the
towering heroes of Grenada.
- Go on, grab it!
- It's like a new dance!
- [Mike] The Army was
looking for sharp people,
and Nick qualified.
- It's pretty kinky!
Hey, guys!
- Nick, thank god you're here!
Something wild is about
to go and let loose!
- I'm here to take you out.
- No, it's some rabid animals!
- [Servo] I don't like
Shari Lewis' new show.
- [Mike] No.
- [Crow] They do a
lot of sit-ups, oh.
(screaming)
(hobgoblins growling)
- [Servo] Nick, lift
your armpit at them!
- [Mike] Just tell us
how to change the music!
- [Servo] Okay, we'll
take your literature,
but we're trying to watch
our program right now.
- Wait here!
- [Crow] Oh, Nick's in
the French army, I see.
- [Mike] Ah, time
for my hourly shave.
- I knew I'd find
a use for this.
- [Servo] So the Army just
hands out grenades, huh?
(screaming)
- Here, I'll.
Just open the door.
Stand back.
- Oh my god, what
do you call that?
- Urban renewal.
- [Crow] Aha, and
what brisk witticism
will this chappie have to offer?
- Wait!
- [Mike] He's fast!
- Ahh!
- [Crow] Look at nothing.
Look at the nothing down there.
- [Servo] Here you go, nothing.
- [Crow] Ha, we drank your
bong water, ha ha ha ha!
Heh heh.
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- Come on.
- Hey, what up
there, Russell Crow?
- Oh, I've set up
a crisis hotline
for people who have
been traumatized
by watching this film.
(phone ringing)
- Hey, hey!
- A customer!
- People and Robots
Who've Had To Watch
The Movie Hobgoblins
Crisis Hotline, hello?
- Oh, oh, yes, hello.
I am in a deep crisis
which is very, very deep,
and I need to know you
won't hang up on me
like all those other
crisis hotlines.
- Ah, have no fear.
I can handle anything.
It is related to watching
the movie Hobgoblins, right?
- Oh, oh, oh, yes, of course,
it relates to watching
the movie Hobgoblins,
that's why I called.
Oh, well, anyway, one day,
I was watching the movie
Hobgoblins one day,
when I realized, while
watching the movie Hobgoblins
that I was in love with
a woman very close to me.
A woman not of my species.
- Ugh, ugh, ugh!
That is disgusting!
I need a shower now, yuck!
- Oh, wait, don't hang up!
I need her, though she
can be very mean to me.
I'm obsessed with her.
I want her in every way.
Emotionally,
spiritually, physically.
- Yuck, stop telling
me this, you freak!
I'm gonna be sick
all over the place!
- Hang up.
- I have another call.
See ya.
- Hang up.
- No, I'll die without her!
She's a chimpanzee,
and her name is Emily!
And I don't care if anyone--
Hello?
Oh, rats, another hang-up.
Well, let's see who's
next on the list.
Butterball Turkey Hotline.
- Ohhh, boy.
I mean, why do these
people even call
if they have nothing
but twisted, perverted
filth on their minds?
- I think it must be
your radiant compassion
that draws them.
(buzzing)
- Probably right, actually.
- Movie sign!
- [Mike] It was
really that bad, huh?
Man, can those little
guys submissively urinate?
- [Servo] Hey, that looks
like a good jumping couch.
- [Mike] Ooh, yeah.
(all sighing simultaneously)
- [Crow] Ah, I need to
cash my $47 paycheck now.
- [Mike] I don't know,
maybe the child lock is on.
Come on.
(growling)
- [Servo] There's a pair
of pink shorts in here
I simply must order!
- [Mike] This guy gets his kicks
by calling about used Vegas.
- [Crow] "Does it have
three on the tree?
"Ooooooh."
(telephone ringing)
- [Servo] Hey look,
there's my mom!
- [Mike] It is!
- Hi.
It's me, Fantazia.
Thanks for calling.
I need a new house pet
to impress my friends.
Now hurry before
the zookeeper comes.
Help me hide this
iguana on my body.
Can I help you, miss?
- [Mike] This is hell, right?
- [Crow] Yes.
- Yes, Mr. Beastmaster.
Something just
crawled up my leg.
Oh, see if you can find it.
I think you better come
back to my office with me.
- [Servo] Mother, get
out of there, please!
- Wait a minute.
Are you sure your office
is in the baboon pit?
Mr. Zookeeper, what do
you think you're doing?
- [Crow] I'm expecting a call.
- [Fantazia] This isn't
the children's petting zoo.
I have a new house
pet for you, miss.
- [Servo] Why are we
watching an insane woman?
- Oh, Mr. Zookeeper.
I could never take a
cockatoo that size.
- [Mike] It's the hobgoblin
with the laughing face.
(sharp screech)
- Oh.
- [Fantazia] Now stop wasting
your money calling me.
I'm right outside your door.
- [Crow] Fran
Drescher out there?
- Don't keep me waiting, lover.
- [Servo] Hey,
here's an idea, guys.
This should be fun.
Whee!
- [Crow] He's bouncing!
- [Servo] Look, I'm having fun!
- [Crow] Like on the couch.
- [Servo] This is fun.
Oh, no, it's not fun, no-o-o-o.
- [Crow] Come on.
- [Servo] No, it is, whee!
Whee-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-haaa, (sobbing)
it's not fun.
- [Mike] It's all right.
I knew it wouldn't be.
I know.
It's okay.
- [Crow] Robert Plant!
(Mike groaning)
(Servo groaning)
- [Mike] That is exactly
what I want to look like.
- [Servo] I don't need
to see every part of
the human anatomy
outlined in spandex.
I can trust it's all there.
- Where's Kyle?
- [Mike] Did they split
a keg of Robitussin?
What are they, get up!
- Did you guys
see where he went?
- [All] No!
- Do you, do you kiss
on the first date?
- I go all the way
on the first date!
- My kind of woman!
- [Crow] Do I have
a friend for you!
- My place or yours?
- Neither.
We'll go to Reputation Road.
- I'll drive.
(gasping pleasurably)
- [Servo] I have to get
my pants a meal first.
- [Mike] Oh, geez, oh, lady,
this is going to be so great--
Oh, wait, oh, I'm done.
Sorry.
- [Servo] So you guys don't
know where he is, then.
- [Mike] I sense the
old man calling me.
- [Crow] Kevin.
- Do we have some time to get
Pop Rocks and whipped cream?
- Just start the car.
- Reputation Road, here we come!
- [Crow] Okay, you
guys, I know a shortcut.
Take Western Avenue.
- Amy, quick, where's
Reputation Road?
- [Mike] You're up!
- Daphne, where's
Reputation Road?
- You go down to the
end of the street.
Make a right, go through
two traffic lights
and up the hill,
and there it is.
So I've heard.
- [Servo] Ah, ha, ha.
- What's going on?
- I don't have time to explain.
It's about those creatures.
I've gotta go across
town and get Kyle.
I want the rest of
you to stay here.
Don't make a move
or do anything.
And above all, don't
fantasize about anything!
- [Servo] Ah, the
rake thing again.
So the movie does make sense!
- [Mike] It's a good movie, see?
- [Servo] It is.
- [Mike] Now see, here, we see
him leaving a parking space.
It's an entirely
different kind of shot.
- [Servo] It's a good movie.
- You know, girls?
I can think of a
fantasy right now.
It's involving the number three.
- [Servo] Three hours
of C.P.O. Sharkey.
- [Crow] Oh, like I'm the pig?
- [Mike] Come to
our club and discuss
cleaning your bathroom tile.
- [Servo] What a clever ad.
I'm going to show
the girls at church.
- [Crow] Ah, painted
by the cast of Hee-Haw.
- [Servo] I guess!
- [Mike] What an aggressive
driving instructor.
- [Crow] Hey.
- [Servo] Uh huh, again,
we see the director
falls back on parking.
- [Mike] It works.
- [Servo] Yup.
- [Crow] It's good stuff.
- [Fantazia] Ah,
don't park here.
- [Kyle] Why not?
- [Mike] It's reserved
for Bob Packwood.
- We have to park near the edge,
if you want to go all the way.
- Oh, yeah, sure!
- [Servo] That's a really
well-thought-out make out spot.
They must get public
funding or something.
(engine turning down)
- [Crow] Ooh, strained zipper.
- How's that?
- Perfect.
- That was some
shortcut you knew about.
I never knew there was a road
through the
children's playground.
- There isn't.
- [Servo] Ha ha, nothing like
a good child endangerment joke!
- Well, what are
you waiting for?
- [Crow] Once and for all,
I really need to
decide my orientation.
- [Servo] Whee!
(Mike sighs)
Oh, forget it.
- Fantazia, where are you going?
- [Mike] Oh, look
out for the hip bone!
- I wanted a better
view of the city.
- [Servo] Can you catch a
venereal disease from a movie?
- You can see it all from here.
(loud crunch)
- [Crow] Ooh, what
just crunched?
Oh.
- Now.
Isn't that a lovely view?
- Oh, it sure is.
- [Mike] The ZZ Top
version of sexuality.
- Where are you going now?
- Just wait a second.
You just keep watching the view.
- [Servo] Keep
watching the view.
- Just hold tight, and get
ready for the ride of your life!
- [Servo] Uh huh.
- Do it to me.
- [Servo] She's the kind
of girl you bring home
to meet mother, if mother's
a cigaretty, retired hooker.
Oh?
- [Crow] Another date is
pushing me off a cliff again.
- [Mike] Rip.
- Need any help?
- Would you get back
inside and wait for me?
This time, don't move!
- [Servo] You
know, this is hell.
You know, now when
we meet people,
we'll be able to report
what hell is like.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- [Crow] That's true.
- We're almost there.
Just think nasty
thoughts while you wait.
(Servo moans dryly)
- [Crow] That is not a
woman, that's David Lee Roth.
- [Mike] Oh, okay,
now I feel grounded.
There's a car pulling
into a driveway.
- [Servo] Camaro, the official
car of peaked in high school.
- [Crow] Her pants
have sapped her energy.
- [Mike] It's an Agnes
De Mille dream ballet!
- [Servo] I'm thinking
of growing a mustache.
What do you think?
- [Crow] It's a bonsai Bigfoot.
- [Servo] (laughing) Kind of.
(hissing)
(sighing)
- [Mike] Back pain is gone.
- Do it to me, baby!
- [Crow] Sell me a quality
muffler at a reasonable price!
- Ah, damn fool!
- What are you doing here?
I want you to meet
my girlfriend.
Wait 'til you see her.
Fantazia?
Honey?
- Kyle, there's no girl!
(Servo crying feebly)
She was a figment
of your imagination.
- No, she's not, she's
just hiding somewhere.
I told you, she's a shy girl.
Sweetie?
- Shy girl?
That bleached blond
witch almost killed you!
- [Servo] The car
will do anything to
get out of the movie.
- She was back there trying to
push your car over the cliff!
Hey, come on!
- Whoa!
- [Crow] In an
unforeseen tragedy,
the two actors
were not in the car
at the time of the crash.
- [Servo] Damn!
(loud explosion)
- [Mike] He makes
an insurance claim
for $700 worth of red shorts.
- [Servo] Their car turned
into a Lincoln and crashed!
- Whoa.
- Now you believe me?
- [Mike] Look at that guy wave
that gel in front of the light!
- [Crow] Eh, come on.
Let's get out there and
wreck another scene, come on.
- [Servo] Ah, that's 30!
30 parking scenes,
I've been counting.
30.
- [Mike] Well, I'm
gonna get my legs waxed.
- I'll discuss my phone
bill with you later.
Oh, no.
They're gone!
(growling)
- [Crow] Drive us
to Chuck E. Cheese!
(growling)
- [Servo] Marty
Allen is attacking!
(growling)
- [Mike] No, you
idiot, that's metric!
- Hit the creature!
- I'm trying to!
- [Crow] Really, the
worst that would happen
is one of those little
plastic eyes would fall out
and you'd choke on it.
- Hit the creature!
- [Servo] The
puppeteer's knuckles
must be very bloody by now.
(grunting)
- Idiot.
- [Mike] This, from an
assistant security guard.
- The creatures broke loose.
Are you guys okay?
- We're doing just fine.
(Servo disgustedly groans)
- What about Amy, where's she?
- She was acting kind of strange
- What, where is she?
- She said she wanted
to go to Club Scum.
- What?
Why didn't you try to stop her?
- And I've seen the police
arresting people there
all the time for God knows what!
- Oh no, come on!
- [Crow] Let's hope it
was a coitus-free van ride
over to Club Scum.
- [Servo] 31!
It's 31.
- [Mike] The Club Scum
courtesy van arrives.
(rock music)
- [Crow] Chord,
chord, chord, chord,
chord, chord, other chord.
Chord, chord, chord,
chord, other chord.
- [Servo] Gary Gaetti!
- Daphne, I think you
got this all wrong!
Amy would never come
to a place like this.
She won't even go through the
mall parking lot by herself.
- Would you just listen to me?
You guys have to have a
certain kind of attitude
when you're in
this part of town.
You gotta look like
you belong, okay?
- [Mike] Like the
overacting extra there.
- Look, would you just listen
to me and nothing will happen.
Now, look, I think one of us
should hold all the
wallets for safekeeping.
You.
- [Servo] Rick Sloane pioneered
the "standing in a stiff line
"near the trouble light" shot.
- Quiet, just be cool.
- Nick?
Kevin, Daphne?
- [Crow] If part
of me is laughing,
I think the part of
me that hates life?
- [Servo] Ah, my insulin!
- [Mike] Oh, it's Debbie
Scum, one of the Scum girls!
(Servo humming music)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where do you guys
think you're going?
- [Crow] Where's your scum?
- We're looking
for a girl in here.
- You know, somehow I don't
think the girls in here
are gonna be your type.
Why don't you try the
Polo Lounge up the street?
Hike it!
Ooh, Daphne!
- [Mike] What happened to you?
- Didn't see you back there.
- Hi!
Roadrash!
Long time, no see.
- I'm sorry to hear
about your boyfriend
coming back from the Army.
You give me a call next
time he's on duty, okay?
- [Crow] Oh, Road!
- Ix-nay on the oldier-say.
Okay?
- [Servo] Look, bite me=ay.
- What?
- Can we go in?
- Now you guys are
friends of Daphne's?
- [Mike] No, you're complete
filth, get in there.
- Go for it, knock
yourselves out.
- [Crow] Hey, Marge Simpson.
- [Servo] You know, this
scene really makes me
want to go clubbing,
the director of this film!
Where is he?
- Do you guys see here anywhere?
- No, would you just sit down
before people start
staring at us?
- [Mike] And I wish I wasn't
staring at any of you!
- [Crow] Oh, say, try
the see bass tonight!
- [Servo] Oh, it's a
Club Scum Christmas.
- Oh, you must be here for the
wet t-shirt contest tonight.
- Wet t-shirt contest?
- [Mike] I could win that!
- Donkey mud wrestling?
- Donkey mud wrestling!
- Get lucky night?
- No!
- [Servo] Ivan
Lendl-lookalike night?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
The donkey mud
wrestlers are supposed
to use the rear entrance.
- [Crow] You're
the expert on that.
- Enjoy the show.
- Hey, Daphne.
- [Servo] Yeah, Club Scum.
- Hi, Daph.
- [Servo] So why are
there lunch ladies
serving tater tots back there?
- Sit down.
- [Crow] They're right, it
is scummy in here, ha ha!
- How do you know
all those guys?
- Just platonic.
- Oh, really?
- Oh, would you
just shut up, okay?
- Hey, you guys aren't
much of a help, you know.
We're supposed to
be looking for Amy.
- [Mike] Willkommen,
bienvenue, welcome.
(emcee clears throat)
(microphone feedback)
- [Servo] Oh,
Satan's on the phone!
- [Mike] That's my
act, good night!
- Greetings, lowlife,
and welcome to Club Scum.
- Hey, get off the stage, idiot!
- [Crow] But you're my manager!
- [Servo] I don't
know, I like him.
(rock music)
- [Mike] Calling
out around the scum,
are you ready for
a brand new filth?
- [Servo] Scummin'
in the Streets.
- [Crow] Ah, this makes
me want to dig out
my extensive Adam
Ant collection.
♪ It's always been my philosophy
- [Servo] Can we get rolls
or breadsticks or something?
- [Mike] I think it's
Ron Reagan's band.
- [Crow] He's singing us
the menu, that's great.
- [Servo] Hoo.
(Servo yodeling)
- [Mike] Looks like she's
dancing on Laugh-In.
- [Crow] Well, then,
sock it to me, Mike.
- [Servo] I find that
very interesting.
- [Crow] Say good night, Mike.
- [Mike] No.
- [Crow] Spoilsport.
- [Mike] Geez.
- [Servo] Oh, this is that
Basque Separatist rock,
I've heard about this.
(Mike clucking like a
chicken to the music)
- [Crow] This is
one of those movies
that's just as famous
for its great soundtrack.
- [Servo] Hobgoblins is
usually on a double bill
with The Harder They Come.
Who am I kidding, no, it isn't.
- [Mike] Jean-Paul Sartre
and the Heartbreakers.
- [Crow] What's weird is that
Nanci Griffith was
the opening act.
She snuck in.
- [Mike] Pig stick, is that
what they're singing, pigs?
Pig sticker, yeah.
- [Servo] I'm not sure.
Pig licker, I think.
So, a man who licks pigs, or
perhaps liquor made from pigs.
- [Mike] I would
not want pig liquor.
- [Servo] I don't know.
- [Mike] She's dancing and
cleaning the acoustic tiles.
- [Servo] The
concert for herpes.
- [Crow] This is a Woody
Guthrie song, right?
- [Servo] Let me tell you about
our drink specials tonight!
Don't park in the alley
or you'll get towed!
While I'm up here, let me
point out the restrooms!
- [Mike] Kid Snickers.
- [Servo] I'm not sure.
- [Crow] Iced chicken?
- [Servo] Oh, it's
Swiss knickers.
- [Mike] Lint kicker.
- [Crow] No, fish picker!
Fish picker, that's our one
song, good night, everybody!
- [Mike] Fish picker!
- [Servo] Fish picker!
(audience applauding)
- [Servo] Woo!
- [Mike] Fish picker!
- [Servo] Woo.
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
- [Mike] Hi, our special
tonight is poached go to hell.
- Get you guys something
to drink, yeah?
- Maybe later.
- There's a two-drink
minimum here.
- Look, we're all
underage, okay?
- [Crow] Okay, then
four goofy grapes.
- Roadrash, come here, quick.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, what is it?
- None of these kids are 21 yet.
- Alright.
How many fake
I.D.s we need here?
- [Servo] Oh, Jock
Itch, you're so helpful!
- This says I'm 40
and handicapped!
- So what?
You got a problem
with that, junior?
- No, I'll limp.
- [Servo] Heh heh.
- [Crow] Funny.
- And now, Club Scum is proud
to present a new headliner.
Appearing nudely and
nightly, Miss Amy Sincere!
(Crow grunts)
- [Servo] Paula Poundstone!
Oh no, oh no.
- Oh my god.
- [Mike] If this is your god,
you have a severe
ontological crisis.
- Amy, get off the stage!
(Servo whines feebly)
- Sit down and shut up!
- [Crow] Yeah,
low-impact aerobics!
- [Servo] Put more clothes on!
- I don't know, but I think
it's sort of an improvement.
- So do I.
(Servo laughing goofily)
- [Crow] Yes, girls,
this is the only way
to make your
boyfriends like you!
- [Mike] Great music.
- [Servo] Uh huh.
- [Mike] Ladies and
gentlemen, Billy Squier!
- [Servo] Wow, you can see
her armpits and everything!
See?
- [Crow] When's the
poetry slam start?
- [Mike] Am I next?
Should I, should I strip too?
- [Crow] You know, she
also does a great fan dance
with an electric window fan.
- [Servo] You know,
this is a great place
to have your kid's
birthday party.
- [Mike] Take the kids
to Club Scum Playland.
- [Servo] The lesser
Kennedys on the town.
- [Crow] Yeah, right down
to the workout gear, mmm!
- [Servo] Great, now try
getting it away from him.
(Crow growling suggestively)
- Bet you showed her how
to do that, huh, Daphne?
- [Mike] Well, I am
a good glove thrower.
- [Servo] It's one
of those cat clocks.
- Well, what do
you think, folks?
Is she a hit, or a miss?
(audience cheering)
- [Crow] They should
really add an S to that.
- [Servo] Hits?
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Mike] I don't.
- Amy, you don't know
what you're doing.
- Hey, get off the stage!
(loud smack)
Amy!
- [Servo] Amy!
(audience cheering)
- [Crow] Wow, they
got a scum-side seat.
- Stop interrupting the show!
- [Servo] And drink your
milk and finish your peas!
- [Mike] She's gonna
take off her hair!
- [Servo] (gulping) That
ziti was a little garlicky.
You gotta tell the chef.
- [Mike] Red-hot
uncensored Jami Gertz.
- [Crow] Just as long as
Demi Moore doesn't come out
and start shaking
her saline bags.
(Servo groaning)
- [Mike] Wow.
Ribbit.
- I want you to
treat me like dirt.
- [Servo] Like fill dirt?
- Spill your drinks on me.
- [Mike] No, they're
four dollars each!
- Show everyone that I'm
not wearing any underwear.
- [Crow] You mean,
under your underwear?
- Take me under the table,
and use me.
Make me.
- [Servo] Prop up the
table if it's uneven.
- Your woman!
- My bike's right outside.
- [Mike] It's a 10-speed.
- I live right around the
corner, you know what I mean?
- Look, she's just drunk.
She doesn't even know
what she's saying.
She's never even been on
the back of a motorcycle.
She's terrified of them.
- [Crow] She's also
afraid of light bulbs!
- Would you guys stop
sitting there and help me?
- Will you help him, Daphne,
seeing that boy with all
the men in this place?
- [Crow] Ha, they
brought in David Mamet
to punch up the dialogue.
- Sergeant Carson, what
are you doing here?
- [Servo] Oh no.
- Howdy, private!
I'm out on a weekend pass.
- [Mike] Ugh, I don't know.
I hear Pixie's working tonight.
- You go out in public
in full uniform?
- A real soldier dies
with his boots on.
- This way, this way!
(feral growling)
- What's going on here?
- Just a problem involving
some small predators, sir!
- [Servo] Oh, this
movie is giving me
current traumatic
stress disorder.
- [Mike] No, okay, hold on.
I got an idea.
Alright, alright, come
with me, come with me.
You guys scram.
I'll just take care of this.
- Private, who's
in command here?
(power tools operating)
(Mike laughing)
(Mike humming)
- [Mike] Okay.
Now I just hit this tape
recorder right here, and--
- [Mike tape] Okay,
here comes this guy.
What's he up to?
- [Servo tape] Boy,
this is stupid.
- [Crow tape] I
wouldn't do that.
Would you?
- [Mike tape] No.
(stilted laughing)
- [Crow tape] Funny.
(doors slamming)
- [Mike] Boy, that sure
is a bad movie, won't you?
- [Servo] It sure is, you know.
- [Crow] Say, fellas,
here's a little song
about that movie, Hobgoblins.
- [Mike] Are you kidding me?
- [Servo] Then, let's go!
♪ Hobgoblins
♪ What do you do
with those hobgoblins
♪ They're over here
♪ They're over there
♪ Those darn hobgoblins
are everywhere
- [Mike] Woo!
- [Servo] Yay!
- Pinky, Brain.
Take a look at this.
Something is different.
♪ As we sing the Hobgoblins song
♪ Today
- I don't know.
Sort of flat,
and lifeless.
- They're cardboard cutouts.
- Exactly, like they're
cardboard cutouts.
- I don't know, I think
they're rockin' today.
- I mean, they actually
are cardboard cutouts.
- They're not that bad.
- You kidding, they're on fire!
- Listen, you idiots!
And Pearl, you, of course, too.
It's a fake Mike and fake
robots made of cardboard, look!
- [Mike] Look out,
here comes one now.
- [Crow] Watch out now,
you little doo-dad.
- [Servo] Something is
sure going to happen.
(cutout creaking)
- [Mike] Well, I
think we all learned
a big lesson about
Hobgoblins today.
(voice on tape distorting)
- Stupid thing, if you could--
- Oh, boy.
♪ Hobgoblins
♪ What do you--
- Run, run!
- You get back into that
theater, Nelson of a--
Try to pull the wool
over my eyes, indeed.
Remember, I'm watching
you, my friend.
Nothing gets by me, nothing!
- Here's a nice fat one for you.
- Oh, thank you.
(Pearl screaming)
Bobo!
(all groaning dejectedly)
- [Servo] Oh, well.
- [Mike] Well, it was
a good thought anyway.
- [Servo] Get rid
of those, will ya?
Ha ha ha, oh no.
That guy tipped
his own table over.
(wild growling)
He did it again!
And yet again!
What is this?
- The crowd here tonight.
- [Mike] They're drinking
too much Oval Brand beer.
(sinister musical cue)
- [Crow] Okay, folks, who
wants a blender drink?
(guttural growling)
- Pixie, did I ever
tell you that I was
a talent scout for a major
motion picture studio?
- [Servo] Did I
ever tell you that
I'm a kneer of bad
actors in the groin?
- Did I ever tell you
that I've always been attracted
to men of your stature?
- [Crow] Five nine, 145 pounds.
- Oh, Pixie!
Pixie!
Oh, Pixie!
Oh!
- [Mike] Oh, right,
Tad, give me a break.
(pained scream)
- [Crow] I don't know who's
getting the worst of it here.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Here.
- [Servo] So why is she
fanning him with a beer bottle?
- Pixie!
(cartoony sound effects)
- Kevin, Kevin!
I got one of them!
- Good, let's hope
it's the right one.
- Oh, Roadrash.
Do it to me!
- [Crow] Scour my
neck with your beard!
- Kevin, quick,
you've gotta stop him!
- Alright.
- Daphne can stay, but I
want you two out of here!
- [Mike] By out of
here, I mean in here!
- Hey, you gotta stop him, look!
- [Servo] Oh, no.
- [Crow] Oh, boy.
(loud explosion)
Still, you could make a case
that this is a better
film than Road House.
- [Servo] Yup.
- [Mike] Stand by for spit take.
(loud explosion)
Spit take away!
- [Servo] Opa!
(loud explosion)
- [Crow] Opa!
- What's all that shouting?
(crowd clamoring)
- [Crow] This is where
his bocce ball training
comes in handy.
(loud explosion)
- [Mike] The hobgoblins
are just waiting outside
'til this blows over.
(loud explosion)
- [Servo] Opa!
- Wait a second.
- [Servo] Oh, Back
Sweat, I love you.
(crowd clamoring)
- [Crow] Go, team, go!
- [Mike] Pepe LePew
came in the back door!
- Wait, stop!
Come back!
- [Mike] Oh, dear.
- [Servo] My t-shirt was
close, I could smell it.
- [Crow] Who wants to see
my new cordless drill?
Anybody?
- [Servo] There's a
phone call for Rick.
Any of you guys Rick?
What?
(gagging)
- [Mike] Ow, oh, big man,
you strangle a plush toy!
(dreamy ethereal music)
- [Servo] Moments later.
- [Crow] Oh, Toe Cheese,
what are you up to now?
- Will you still fake
your (bleep) for me?
- Fake this!
(glass crashing)
- [Servo] That's Butt Crack!
- Hey, look!
There's Amy!
- [Mike] We gotta help
her finish stripping!
- Amy!
Are you okay?
- I'm not sure.
Why am I dressed like
a rock video slut?
- It's a long story,
I'll explain later.
- [Crow] Stallone.
Scum.
Opens Friday.
- Name, rank, serial number?
- Don't shoot me!
I'm just an employee.
I don't even book
the talent here.
- [Servo] Proof there is
no life after drama club.
- [Mike] Ruben Kincaid!
- Sergeant, can you stop him?
- Why?
This is the best
training he's ever had!
You could never get
this at boot camp.
- You call that training?
He could kill somebody!
- War isn't pretty.
- Daphne and Nick
are still inside.
We gotta try and help 'em.
- Maybe I should send Nick off
to some third-world country?
That would give you all
the time that you need.
- Let go of me!
- Maybe I could
get Nick out of the
picture altogether?
Nick, this is your
sergeant speaking!
Save the troops!
That's an order!
- Nick, no!
Don't do it!
- [Servo] So, why hand grenades?
Are there foot grenades?
(loud explosion)
- [Mike] My fajita plate was
really hot and I touched it!
(Nick screaming)
- [Crow] Ahh.
Ahh.
- [Servo] Ahh.
- [Crow] It's okay,
I wore my flame suit
and jellied my skin today.
No problem.
- [Servo] Hoo, the smell of
all that smoldering back hair.
- The truck of soldiers
is waiting outside.
It'll be a dream come true.
- [Mike] You feel
a hand inside yoU?
Uncomfortable, huh?
- [Servo] Sure is!
- My dream can come
true right now!
- [Crow] My beautiful
dream from my childhood
of exploding
another human being!
(loud explosion)
- I got the last of them.
- [Servo] Now who
are these guys?
Have we seen them
in the movie yet?
- [Crow] The tall
guy looks familiar.
- [Servo] I'm not
sure who it is.
I don't know.
- [Mike] Ugh, foot
odor too strong.
Ugh.
- [Crow] Could someone make
a joke about my promiscuity?
Please?
- [Servo] Sweat Gland
surveys the carnage.
- Must have been a
rowdy crowd tonight.
- Hey, hey!
Hey, Ms. Sincere.
You know, I really liked that
show you were doing inside.
- Hey, scumball,
the show is over.
Why don't you just climb
back under your rock?
- Daphne, I could
have done that!
(Servo whines feebly)
- Oh, sorry.
- Amy, I want you to know that
I'll always be there for you.
- Well, you know,
no one's ever really
noticed me before like that.
I mean, I've always just been
thought of as Daphne's friend.
This is the first time somebody
came up to me like that.
I kinda liked it.
- Amy, I meant what I said.
I'm gonna prove it to you.
- [Mike] Now come on, Nick--
Oh, yeah, he burned to death.
Oh, well!
- [Crow] Nick's a
smoking husk right now.
He won't mind if
we take his van.
(van engine turning)
- [Servo] Anyone want to
stop at Carl's Jr., huh?
- [Mike] Oh, why
did Hoover lose?
- Where is he?
- [Crow] The angel of death.
I've been waiting so long!
(Mystery Science
Theater 3000 theme)
Hey, it's a common man
with his common van.
- [Servo] I don't think so.
- [Mike] Must be act three.
Things are moving
really fast now.
- [Servo] Yep.
- Mr. McCreedy?
- [Crow] We're out
of the van now.
We can start the scene.
- Hey, there.
- [Servo] Oh no, Mike,
who are these people now?
- [Crow] Yeah, I don't.
- We have a score to settle.
- [Mike] But first, I'm gonna
hit myself with road flares.
- [Crow] No, I only
work with rakes, okay?
- Amy?
This time I'm gonna
make you proud.
- [Servo] Ow.
Ow, ow, ow, owie, ow, ow, ow.
Ow, my back.
Ow, ow, oh, ow, owie, ow, ow.
(Servo laughing)
- [Mike] Filipino push fighting.
- [Servo] (laughing) I guess.
- Amy, I think Kevin's
proved his bravery to you.
Would you tell him to stop
before he kills himself?
- For God's sake, Kevin,
stop before you he kills you!
- [Servo] Or after he kills
you would be fine by me.
- [Mike] Imagine getting
beat up by a guy named Kevin.
- [Servo] Doo-doo-doo-doo.
- [Crow] Now, come on,
that move really requires
the cooperation of the flippee.
- [Servo] Put a grenade
down his pants, that works.
- [Mike] Amy, look,
I'm a man, did you see?
(Servo imitating sexy music)
- [Servo] Oh.
- Sometimes you win.
Sometimes you lose.
- [Crow] Sometimes when we
touch, the honesty's too much.
(gun clicks)
- No!
- [Servo] Please.
(loud bang)
- [Mike] I shot you
instead, is that okay?
- [Servo] Ah, my
finger's in the door!
Ow, wow!
(dreamy ethereal music)
- [Crow] And he's assumed
into B-movie heaven.
- I'm sorry for sending
you out on your own.
I should have
known the creatures
would try to destroy you also.
(hobgoblins growling)
- Where are they going now?
(Servo whines feebly)
- Back to their
home in the vault.
Hurry, there isn't
much time left.
- Kevin, wait.
- [Mike] What, what?
What do you want?
Why would you pull me back here?
Why did you tell me to wait?
So, what'd you call me back for?
- Don't take too long.
I'll be waiting.
- Let's go!
- [Crow] I think he's
trying to tell us something!
What is it, boy?
- [Mike] Damn, I
thought you was into me.
- Go, come!
- [Crow] Slutting's
fun, isn't it?
Yeah.
(Servo panting)
- [Servo] No, no, slower!
More bandy-legged!
- [Mike] Let's go for a
ride on a Clarke-a-Matic.
- Do you think--
- Shh.
- [Crow] Quit
screaming like that!
(guttural growling)
- I was right about them.
They're back inside.
- [Mike] And they're
smoking hams.
- Maybe we should get closer
and lock them back inside again.
- No, I spent 30
years guarding them.
I was fired from my job tonight.
I won't be around here
to keep an eye on them.
- You were fired?
- [Servo] No, he was the
backbone of this place!
- Well, maybe I could
guard them from now on.
- Oh, no.
I don't want you to throw your
life away the way I had to.
- [Mike] Destroy your
life in your own way!
- There is a better way.
(Mike groaning)
- Did you find them?
- Yeah, they're back
inside the vault.
- What are you gonna do to them?
- I don't know.
- Kevin.
Did I ever tell you
what I did in the war?
- No.
- [Crow] Shot off
my toe and got out.
- Munitions.
(detonator beeping)
(loud explosion)
- [Servo] It was supposed
to unlock the van door!
- [Mike] Whoops.
- [Servo] I just blew
up the studio accountant
for no reason, hehehehe.
- Isn't it ironic
that they should pick
a movie studio to land?
- [Crow] You think?
- Unless they figured they
belonged in a dream factory.
(Mike laughs nervously)
- [Mike] Come away from
the weird security guard.
- You were my hero tonight.
- [Servo] You got some
spinach stuck in your teeth.
- What?
Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
- [Crow] She's made her decision
and they're going
ahead with the sex.
- [Servo] Yay!
- Daphne?
- Yeah?
- This is for you.
- [Mike] I blotted up
some grape juice for you.
- Really?
No one's ever given
me flowers before!
- Oh, but there's lots of things
I could show you
for the first time.
Nick.
- Nick?
- Nick!
- Daph!
Baby!
(everyone retching)
- Told you guys I had
everything under control.
- [Servo] Well.
- Daphne?
- Nicky?
- [Both] Van!
- [Crow] So, the results
of his complete immolation
is just minor redness
and irritation.
- [Mike] Gonna call
the Sears and Roebuck
and get some dry goods.
- Hello, Mr. Comstock.
Yes, I realize what time it is.
I'm sorry to wake you, sir, but,
there's been an
accident at the studio.
- [Crow] We made Hobgoblins.
- The film vault blew up.
Yes, the building
is still smoldering.
Yes, I realize
about the insurance,
but you fired me earlier.
- [Servo] Uh huh.
There was no one on duty.
- [Servo] Course not.
- When it happened.
- [Servo] Guys,
I'll be right back.
- [Mike] Oh, okay.
- Excuse me, sir.
Could I use your phone?
- [Crow] You know, Mike, one
thing I learned from this movie
is that Daphne is a slut,
and Amy wasn't fun
until she became a slut.
- [Mike] Oh, that's the
fun message of toda--
- [Servo] Mike, a
little help here?
- [Crow] What's he up to?
- [Mike] Yeah, what do you need?
- [Servo] Come over here.
Rick Sloane's out here,
and he needs a little help.
- [Mike] Rick Sloane?
- [Servo] Yeah, Rick
Sloane, the director.
- [Mike] He's here, right now?
- [Servo] Yeah, the director
of today's movie, Rick Sloane.
Wanted to explain a few
things about his film.
Hello, am I speaking
English here?
- [Mike] Okay, just seems
a little weird, is all.
Rick Sloane actually--
- [Servo] Well, he is.
- [Mike] Oh, oh, I see.
Yeah, yeah.
You know, Rick Sloane is
lighter than you think.
- [Servo] Oh, oh, is he, Mike?
Well, I guess I had no
preconceived notions
about Rick Sloane's weight.
I guess I'm not a racist
like you are, Mike!
- [Mike] Okay, but--
- [Servo] So, Rick Sloane,
director of Hobgoblins.
How are you?
Crow!
- [Crow] What?
- [Servo] The voice.
Perhaps you could be
of some assistance
in helping Mr.
Rick Sloane explain
some of the things
about the film?
- [Crow] Oh, hey, he seems nice,
but I've never met
the guy before.
- [Servo] Would you just
do the voice, Crow?!
- [Crow] Ohh,
right, right, right.
- [Servo] So, Mr. Rick Sloane.
- [Crow] Hello, and how are you?
- [Servo] Good, good.
Say, why don't you explain to
the good folks exactly what--
- [Crow] Good!
May I just say how nice
it is to meet you all.
My accommodations
are just lovely,
and everyone's been so nice.
Rarely have I been treated--
- [Servo] Could we just
please talk about your film?
- [Crow] Certainly,
certainly, my film, yes.
- [Servo] Yes, yes, okay.
When you came up with
the idea for Hobgoblins,
were you high on crack?
Say yes.
- [Crow] Yes, yes,
I had been doing
quite a bit of crack
that day as I recall.
- [Servo] Yes, yes, good, good.
That helps me understand
it just a bit.
Now another question I'm
sure everyone who has seen
the movie Hobgoblins
has on their lips,
and forgive me if I don't phrase
this in just the right way.
Are you, in fact, a total idiot?
Say yes!
- [Crow] Yes, yes, I am
an idiot, that is correct.
How penetratingly intelligent
for you to notice.
- [Mike] You know, Servo, I
couldn't help but notice--
- [Servo] Stay
out of it, Nelson.
- [Mike] Okay.
- [Servo] Now, director of
this film, Mr. Rick Sloane,
another question that I've
been asked to put to you
by the legions who have
enjoyed your film Hobgoblins.
Did someone open up your skull
and carefully replace your
brains with rat droppings?
Say yes.
- [Crow] Yeah, I'm on it.
Yes, yes, once again, your
insight is quite correct.
I was home one night
right before the filming
of my hit film Hobgoblins,
when I received an
unsolicited call
suggesting I try their service,
wherein they replaced my
brains with rat droppings.
It was a good deal,
so I said yes.
- [Servo] Good, good,
another mystery solved.
Well, thank you for your time.
- [Mike] Actually,
Servo, I think
you have time for
another question.
- [Servo] Oh, really?
Oh, gee, I wasn't
really prepared.
Well, Rick, how are you, then?
- [Crow] As I stated
before, I'm good, thank you.
- [Servo] Good, so.
Rick Sloane.
Good.
Do you have any hobbies at all?
- [Crow] Nope.
- [Servo] Really?
No hobbies?
- [Crow] None.
- [Mike] Okay,
you're off the hook.
We gotta get out of here.
- [Servo] Thank you.
Bye, Rick.
(doors slamming)
Good work, Servo.
Nice job.
- Hey, clownpants.
- Hey there, Mike.
You know how we
really didn't care
for that stupid movie today?
Well, by using our time machine,
I went back to the early 80s,
and I took care of our
little Rick Sloane problem,
if you know what I mean.
- What?
Servo, you don't,
you don't mean you--
- Yeah, I sure did, Mike.
I hunted down Rick Sloane,
and I kicked him, Mike,
right in his shin!
I'm sorry, friend,
it's gruesome, I know,
but I had to take matters
into my own hands.
- Well, I thought, you
know, you'd gone back
and terminated him, you know?
- What do you mean, terminated?
Terminate, what are you, nuts?
I hate guns, I hate them!
How could you ever
get that idea, man?
- I don't know.
- Well, anyway, by going
back and giving our Mr. Sloan
a firm, swift blow to the shin,
I have changed the
course of events,
and Hobgoblins is no more.
- Hey, hey, hey-hey,
hey, you guys!
I'm doing my biography
of Rick Sloane here,
doing my research,
and listen to this.
Rick Sloane says the inspiration
for his film Hobgoblins
is like a stout red automaton
kicking him in the shins.
- Stout?
Stout, he says stout?
Bastard, I'm going
back to kill him.
- No, no.
You know, I gotta put a child
lock on our time machine.
- Good idea.
- Mike.
Servo.
Art.
I took away the couch and
brought it back down here.
You are all old enough to be
taking some responsibility
for some of our things.
Couches do not grow on trees.
- Hey, can I have some of
your Welch's Grape Juice?
- Sure, if I can have
some of that seal coat!
- You bet!
- There was a nice satay I was
thinking of sending up there.
There was a particular
office chair
I know you would
have enjoyed, Crow,
but I don't know that
I can ever trust you
with any home
furnishings ever again.
Bobo, Brain Guy.
Who wants candy?
- Oh, I do, I do!
Me!
- I don't mean to yell.
(loud explosion)
I just really want everyone
to stay off the couch.
(Bobo groaning)
(somber music)
(funky music)
(guttural growling)